Guide to the Stanford News Service Audiovisual Recordings SC1125
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Videorecordings, 1936-2011; Series 2
  - Stanford Campus Views, 05/17/1993; 93-0517-2; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    CAMPUS VIEWS T9 WHEELCHAIR: 00:43 Wide shot Quad; 00:44 Zoom in, medium shot walls and arch; 00:57 Wide shot Quad; 01:23 Zoom in to medium shot Quad; 01:40 Wide shot Quad; 01:57 Zoom in to medium shot walls and arch; 02:11 Wide shot tower and parking lot; 02:37 New wide shot of tower and lot; 02:50 Zoom in, until 03:04 medium shot of tower; 03:11 Close up tower; 03:15 Zoom out to medium shot tower top; 03:24 Zoom out to medium shot and lot; 03:42 Wide shot campus Quad--static; 04:17 Zoom in slow until 04:44, medium shot wall and three arches; 04:51 Zoom out, wide shot quad; 04:57 Close up wall; 05:01 Pan crazily around until 05:08, wide shot Quad; 05:38 Medium shot wall and three arches; 05:54 Zoom out, wide shot Quad; 06:20 Zoom out, wider shot Quad; 06:31 Zoom out, wider shot quad; 06:48 Zoom in brief, zoom out quickly; 06:57 Zoom in, medium shot wall and three arches; 07:14 Medium shot of there arches; 07:30 Medium shot of wall and three arches; 07:34 Medium shot of wall and three arches; 07:42 Wide shot wall and three arches; 07:57 Zoom out until 08:07, wide shot quad; 08:15 Zoom in, wide shot wall and three arches; 08:26 Look up at wall top, wide shot; 08:30 Wide shot detail on wall, camera trembles; 08:35 Medium shot arch and wall; 08:56 Zoom out, wide shot wall and three arches; 09:11 Zoom out, wide shot Quad; 09:24 Zoom in quick, medium shot wall; 10:08 Wide shot mansion center; 10:26 New wide shot mansion center; 10:50 Zoom in until 11:00, medium shot arch doorway; 11:10 Zoom out, wide shot center; 11:46 Medium shot of windows; 12:02 Medium shot center; 12:16 Pan left, medium shot tree, side if building; 12:21 Medium shot building corner; 12:34 Medium shot of center building; 12:48 Wide shot of center; 13:31 Medium shot Business School sign. Static; 14:02 Close up business School sign. Static; 14:08 Pan around crazy until 14:17; 14:17 Medium shot people walking; 14:23 Pan left; 14:29 Pan left again; 14:40 Medium shot of students across stairs; 14:52 Medium shot, student coming down; 14:57 Medium shot of Business School sign; 15:04 Close up Business School sign; 15:07 Medium shot of Business School sign; 15:16 Medium shot people in courtyard; 15:43 Medium shot people at tables; 16:02 Zoom out, wide shot tower and tables; 16:14 Medium shot of tower; 16:32 Pan right, medium shot of tables; 16:41 Medium shot tower; 16:47 Wide shot tables; 16:54 Zoom in and out, wide shot tables; 17:15 Medium shot students at table; 17:36 Pan right on other students, medium shot; 17:45 Pan far right, medium shot of students; 18:12 Medium shot Business School sign, static; 18:36 Zoom in; 18:53 Wide shot Quad amphitheater--static; 19:29 Medium shot tower; 19:55 Zoom out; 20:01 zoom out, wide shot amphitheater; 20:36 Medium shot amphitheater; 20:56 Medium shot ivy arch and palm trees. Static; 23:00 Close up ivy arch. Static; 23:41 Medium shot people walking under arch; 23:56 Zoom out, wide shot arch through lamppost; 24:14 Wide shot class change; 24:17 Medium shot of bikers; 24:32 Wide shot class change; 24:38 Wide shot tour group, group passes on right; 25:05 Medium shot back of tour group; 25:25 Medium shot individual backs; 25:46 Medium three-shot of people's backs; 26:11 Wide shot of people on road; 26:34 Medium shot of bikers; 26:36 Medium shot as bikers pass; 27:07 Medium shot as bikers pass; 27:47 Zoom in, bikers passing; 28:38 Medium three shot of people and bag; 28:51 Medium shot of people on road; 29:10 Wide shot of road; 29:20 Medium shot as bikers pass; 29:31 Wide shot of people on road; 29:52 Medium shot of road; 31:06 Wide shot of road; 31:29 Medium three-shot of students; 31:43 Medium shots of students passing by; END
  - Stanford campus views, 05/17/1993; 93-0517-3; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    00:19:50
    STANFORD CAMPUS VIEWS 1993: Memorial Church; quad; Baseball
    Stanford Campus Views Tape Log, tape 3 (13:22 red map graphic): 00:55 Pan out to wide shot of Quad; 01:30 Medium shot, man and woman in Quad walking toward camera; 01:41 Slow pan out to wide shot; 02:25 Wide shot, pan to left from arches to palm trees and (? building); 03:04 Pan down from church to arch walkway long shot; 03:26 Pan from arches to Hoover Tower; 03:40 Medium shot, Hoover; 04:06 Medium shot, camera follows cyclist, up close cyclist rides out of shot at 04:17; 04:21 Medium shot, Hoover; 04:54 Camera follows student cyclist, cyclist rides away from camera out of shot; 05:27 Close up of Crucifixion with a few organ notes; 05:29 Pan out to three windows in background and two people looking at them (windows are very clear, everything else very dark); 05:57 Same shot, lightened up overall (bumped up); 06:16 Organ music; 06:27 Close up, angels window; organ music; 06:49 Close up, another angel--focus to blur; organ music; 07:08 Close up, first angels window -- focus to blur (wobbly); organ music; 07:19 close-up, same angels--quick focus to blur; organ music stops as blur
    EVERYTHING BELOW IS BAD 07:29 Medium shot, arches shot of church; 07:33 Pan up to top of church; 08:03 Quick close-up of top of church Biblical scene; 08:14 Zoom onto three small church windows; 08:30 Medium shot, three small and main big church window; 08:52 Close up, angel and baby on side of church; 09:20 Close up, part of top of arch on church; 09:41 Pan out of church arches with cyclists riding by; 10:11 Pan up from three church arches to Biblical scene at top of church; 10:48 Close up and quick pan out of cross on main church outside window; 10:56 Close up, top of main church window; 11:34 Close up, Faith angel on church wall; 11:44 Pan out of medium close-up of angel; 12:02 Medium shot, pan up from people walking through church archway up to top of church; 12:22 Wide shot, church through archway (wrong exposure?) with some people crossing field; 13:32 Close up of Jesus on church outside; 13:34 Close up, pan out to arch view; 13:58 Wide shot, church front (straight on) with students passing by; 14:34 Same shot, cyclist rides away from camera, tour group walks from behind camera; 16:59 Medium shot, man and woman talking in arch walkway with columns in background; 17:29 Wide shot, man and woman talking; 18:19 Medium shot, from inside walkway through arch out onto Quad; 18:51 Same shot, zoom onto male and female student walking through Quad; 19:08 Medium shot, three women with two bikes talking and getting stuff together to go; 19:40 Medium close, male student lying on grass, reading; 20:20 Close up, back of male student; 20:25 Pan out to reveal Rodin sculpture; 20:45 Wide shot, arches in Quad with red flowers in front
  - Stanford Campus Views, 05/17/1993; 93-0517-4; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    Noon Hoover Clock Tower; Fountain; Hoover; Green Library; Archways; Quad
  - Stanford campus views, 05/20/1993; 93-0520-2; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    00:25:02
    STANFORD CAMPUS VIEWS 1993: Memorial Church; Quad and church; Students in science lab
    00:05 Medium shot of students in hallways; 00:10 Wide shot of arches and students walking through hallways; 00:40 Zoom in on students walking through arches; 01:00 Zoom out to show columns; 01:20 Camera follows cyclist, cyclist moves on; 01:40 Wide shot of arches and hallway from Quad, palm trees visible; 01:50 Zoom out to wider shot; 02:15 Medium of couple walking through arch; 02:40 Widen to show whole arch; 03:00 Zoom back in to show tourists and group under arch; 03:20 Zoom out to show people standing in front of arch shot is taken through another arch on opposite side of Quad; 04:24 Zoom into medium shot of three arches and people in front; 04:40 Wide shot of ivory tower and buildings; 04:55 Close up of tower, zoom out to wide shot of buildings and people; 05:10 Medium shot, people walking in front; 05:30 Close up tower, zoom out to tower and buildings; 05:49 Cyclist and walkers in front of buildings, shot widens to include tower; 06:14 Wide shot of church as shown through arch across Quad; 06:30 Close up of cross on top of church; 06:43 Zoom out to full shot of church through arch across Quad; 07:06 Zoom in, medium shot of biker, biker goes off camera; 07:25 Close up of Jesus on church wall; 07:40 Medium shot of church wall and stained glass; 07:45 Close up middle stained glass; 07:55 Wide shot of church; 08:18 Medium shot of people walking in front of church; 08:25 Medium shot of church; 08:40 Close up detail of church wall; 09:05 Close up of Jesus on wall and other detail on wall, static; 09:53 Medium shots of doorways to church, angels with babies; 10:10 Close-ups of angels on wall: Faith, Hope, Charity, Love with two babies; 10:40 Medium shot of church doorways; 10:53 Medium shots of tour. Tour guide describes history of campus, walk toward church; 11:57 Close up exterior shot of plaque about the church on church wall, zoom up to church wall with the angel "Love"; 12:24 Inside the church of banner hanging off the ceiling; 12:30 Medium shot of tour group going inside; 12:45 Close up of stained glass inside church, zooms to tour group and then back to window; 13:20 Different glass window, with Jesus, organ music plays in background; 13:40 Zoom out to see banner close to stained glass window, organ music; 14:20 Zoom out to show wide shot of church; 14:30 Left tilt to show medium shot of balcony inside church; 14:55 Wide shot of church outside; 15:11 Zoom out to show entire Quad, can see steeple of church; 15:25 Zoom back in to show wide shot of church; 15:43 See medium of arches leading into church, people entering through arches; 16:06 Wide shot of Quad and church in back; 16:23 Zoom in to see arch doorways and people going towards church; 16:50 Medium shot of church; 16:57 Wide shot of tower and palm trees; 17:10 Close up of tower, zoom out to wide shot of palm trees and tower; 17:30 Cut to student in lab; 17:44 Pan left to show equipment; 17:50 Medium shot of two students; 18:00 Close up equipment, zoom back out to have medium two shot of students; 18:20 Close up of students, first back of on one then side of the other; 18:40 Close up of graph printed by students; 19:00 Medium two shot of students; 19:15 Close up of student's gloves; 19:29 Medium shot of other students in the lab; 19:35 Close up of student in lab; 19:50 Close up of sample on burner; 20:00 Medium shot of students in lab; 20:15 Close up of students performing experiments; 20:51 Zoom in and out on different students; 21:20 Medium shot through machine wires of student and experiment; 21:30 Close up on student; 21:41 Pan of lab and students; 21:50 Close up student; 22:00 Overhead pan of lab; 22:19 Close up of student's notes; 22:30 Overhead pan of lab; 22:40 Close up through machine wires of student working; 23:00 Widens to medium shot; 23:20 Medium two shot of students working on experiments in lab; 23:52 Close up of experiment; 24:05 Medium of student; 24:20 Medium shot of students working on different experiment; 24:35 Close up of experiments; 24:59 Zoom out to full shot of lab; 25:52 Close up of students in lab; 25:07 Medium shot of students working in lab
  - Stanford campus views with Condoleezza Rice, 05/24/1993; 93-0524-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    00:20:40
    STANFORD CAMPUS VIEWS; CONDOLEEZZA RICE 1993: Condoleezza Rice on Quad; Foreign Policy class; Stills of George Bush and Colin Powell with Condoleezza
    Tape log Tape #1: 00:35 Close up Condoleezza Rice; 01:001 Condoleezza meets woman in Quad; jokes about camera; 01:18 Close up, camera follows two women; 01:30 Close up on back of two women going inside building; 01:50 Close up Condoleezza going up stairs; 02:06 Condoleezza meets man on stairs; close-up two shot, also joke about camera; 02:28 Camera follows Condoleezza going inside classroom; 02:50 Medium shot inside classroom with students; 03:15 Close up Condoleezza, zoom out to wide shot of classroom; 03:40 Cut to close-up of Condoleezza; 03:45 Zoom out to wide of classroom; 03:57 Wobbly pan of classroom; 04:07 Close up of Condoleezza; 04:24 Wide shot, classroom; 05:33 Close up Condoleezza, widens to left-right pan of students and class; 06:05 Close up of student; 06:23 Pan left to Condoleezza, close-up of Condoleezza; 06:39 Pan left and close-up of student; 06:50 Pan right, close-up of Condoleezza; 07:25 Pan left to student, students talks off camera; 07:46 Medium shot of class; 08:06 Wide shot of classroom, quick tighten to medium shot of class; 08:57 Wide shot of class, elbow sticks in camera; 09:10 Close up of Condoleezza; 09:56 Medium shot of classroom; 10:09 Close-ups of students; 10:42 Medium shot, speaker's back close up talk about GATT; 11:26 Medium shot, Condoleezza discusses GATT; 11:55 Close up Condoleezza discusses French wars; 12:40 Zoom out on wide shot of class; 12:53 Medium three shot of students; 13:07 Wide shot of class; discusses Germany's role in trade policy; 13:55 Medium shots of Condoleezza; 14:45 Wide shot of class; 15:02 Medium shot of student, talking about French agriculture, psychological aspects; 15:45 Close up of student, also talking about France; 16:10 Close up of Condoleezza, speaker off camera; 16:36 Medium to close shots of students, same speaker; 16:43 Still of George Bush staff, including Condoleezza, medium shot; 17:09 Close up of Bush, pan right to Condoleezza; 17:21 Close back to Bush, pan back right to Condoleezza; 17:43 Medium shot still of Colin Powell with Condoleezza; autograph on photo says "With admiration and best wishes for continued success"; 18:42 Close up Colin and Condoleezza; 19:06 Medium still of Bush staff and Condoleezza; 19:35 Camera dips off screen; 19:47 Close up Bush and Condoleezza, slight zoom in zoom out; 20:04 Zoom out on still; 20:12 Zoom in close-up of Bush and Condoleezza; 20:26 Zoom out on still; 20:34 Zoom in; Out of focus camera until 20:55; 21:04 Close up Bush and Condoleezza; 21:15 Medium shot, close-up, zoom out, close-up, zoom out; END
    Discussion: During opening scenes with the two people she met on the Quad and in the building, Rice was sociably talking about the camera, saying hello, etc. In the classroom the discussion was about foreign trade policy, namely GATT. The students had turned in papers that week about countries involved in the agreements: Great Britain, France, Germany, Russia (which was deemed out of the loop) and other countries. Most of the papers were focused on France. The students discussed topics having to do with GATT and what made the countries, especially France, behave the way they did. Afterward the camera went to stills of photos and there was no sound.
  - Stanford Baccalaureate Ceremony-Tape 1, 06/12/1993; 93-0612-1a; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    00:27:26
    STANFORD BACCALAUREATE 1993: Kennedy Grove; Entrance of graduates; Stanford Band; President's speech; Graduates and parents
    00:20 Medium shot flag bearers and graduates; 00:35 Zoom out, wide shot auditorium; 00:51 Medium shot flag bearers and graduates; 01:29 Zoom out; 01:32 Pan right, medium shot parents; 01:40 Pan left, medium shot parents; 01:50 Medium two-shot spectators; 01:57 Medium two-shot flag bearers; 02:09 Zoom out to wide shot of graduates; 02:22 Medium shot flag bearers and graduates; 02:37 Medium three-shot of graduates; 02:43 Medium shot follows flag bearers upstage; 02:52 Medium shot graduates file in; 03:04 Wide shot graduates file in; 03:16 Wide shot auditorium; 03:23 Close up man in red and blue robe; 03:28 Pan left, medium shot as grads file in; 03:45 Pan right, camera goes through sea of grads, medium shot; 04:08 Medium shot grads filing in; 04:10 Camera goes through sea of grads, medium shot; 04:47 Close up graduate; 04:54 Pan right onto parents and left onto grads; 05:00 Close up parent; 05:02 Close up kilt; 05:08 Close up parent; 05:12 Pan left, close-up parents; 05:25 Pan left over parents; 05:35 Wide shot auditorium; 05:43 Zoom out wider; 05:53 Medium three-shot band members; 06:00 Close up sign; 06:06 Medium three-shot band members; 06:14 Medium shot grads file in; 06:25 Zoom out, wide shot auditorium; 06:46 Zoom in until 07:01 medium shot grads file in; 07:21 Medium shot parents; 07:31 Medium shot grads; 07:57 Medium shots of grad faces; 08:00 Pan right over grads until 08:15; 08:15 New medium shot of grads; 08:25 Zoom up medium shot; 08:34 Close up flag bearer; 08:39 Zoom out; 08:47 Close up Fargo in red and blue robe; 08:49 Medium two shots of grads; 09:30 Close up President Casper; 09:35 Zoom out, camera follows Casper up stairs to stage; 09:49 Medium three-shot on stage; 09:57 Close up Stanford sign; 10:01 Zoom out to full stage; 10:11 Wide shot grads; 10:15 Close up drum player; 10:20 Close up speaker; 10:29 Zoom out to wide shot, drum players and stage; 10:45 Pan left, wide shot grads; 10:52 Medium two-shot; 10:58 Medium three shot of drummers; 11:19 Close up drummers; 11:23 Pan left onto other drummers, medium shot; 11:35 Close up drumsticks; 11:39 Zoom out, medium shot drummers; 11:49 Pan left, medium shot all drummers; 12:09 Close up drummer; 12:18 Pan left, close-up musician; 12:31 Pan right, medium shot musicians from ground; 12:51 Pan right, medium shot drummers; 13:02 Medium shot stage and musicians; 13:16 Pan right, wide shot grads; 13:24 Medium three shot grads; 13:29 Pan left over grads, medium shot; 13:42 Medium shot grads, pan right over; 13:53 Pan right; 14:01 Medium three-shot; 14:09 Close up grad; 14:11 Zoom out; 14:24 Medium shot speaker; 14:34 Zoom out until 14:37, medium shot stage; 14:45 Medium shot stage, speakers; 14:56 Medium shot stage; 15:08 Medium three shot; 15:16 New medium three-shot; 15:30 Medium shot Casper; 15:36 Zoom out to medium shot stage; 15:52 Close up speaker; 16:07 Pan right, medium shot Casper; 16:15 Zoom out to medium shot stage. Static; 16:45 Medium shot people onstage; 16:54 Medium three shot; 17:01 Pan left over stage; 17:12 Close up man in graduation hat onstage; 16:54 Medium three shot; 17:01 Pan left over stage; 17:12 Close up man in graduation hat onstage; 17:22 Medium shot onstage; 17:29 Close up man without hat onstage; 17:41 Wide shot grads; 17:51 Medium shot grads and parents; 18:03 Medium shot Casper's back; 18:10 Close up Casper's back; 18:20 Zoom out to medium shot; 18:29 Medium three-shot onstage; 18:42 Wide shot onstage; 18:51 Close up speaker getting up from seat; 19:06 Close up speaker; 19:22 Zoom out to wide shot stage; 19:41 Close up Casper; 19:50 Zoom out, medium shot stage; 19:58 Zoom out, wide shot stage; 20:15 Medium shot grads; 20:22 Close up Teva sandals; 20:28 Medium three-shot; 20:32 Wide shot auditorium; 20:39 Medium shot grads; 20:51 Zoom in, medium shot grad faces; 21:03 Pan left to wide shot auditorium; 21:11 Medium shot two grads; 21:20 Medium three-shot parents; 21:32 Close up two grads; 21:42 Close up grad; 21:50 Pan left, close-up grad; 21:58 Pan left, close-up grads; 22:58 Zoom out, wide shot grads; 23:05 Medium shot parents; 23:23 Medium shot parent; 23:30 Medium shot, sea of parents; 23:38 Zoom out until 23:46, wide shot auditorium; 23:50 Medium shot of four grads; 24:00 Zoom out to medium shot of all grads; 24:24 Pan right over grads; 24:39 Close up grads; 24:43 Zoom out over grads; 24:59 Medium shot of speaker over grads; 25:04 Medium three shot of parents; 25:11 Medium shots of parents; 25:34 Pan left, medium shots parents; 25:46 Medium three-shot; 25:51 Close up parent; 25:53 Pan left, close-up parent; 25:58 Medium three-shot parents; 26:02 Wide shot auditorium and tower; 26:24 Medium shot auditorium and stage; 26:35 Zoom out to wide shot stage and auditorium; 26:50 Zoom in to medium shot stage and auditorium; 27:00 Medium shot woman in wheelchair; 27:10 Medium shot parents in back of auditorium; 27:19 Zoom out; 27:26 Pan left, wide shot auditorium and tower; END
  - Stanford Baccalaureate Ceremony-Tape #2, 06/12/1993; 93-0612-1b; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    00:11:42
    STANFORD BACCALAUREATE 1993 Kennedy Grove Time capsule ceremony; Senior lunch; Cutaway camera
  - Stanford Baccalaureate Ceremony-Tape #3, 06/12/1993; 93-0612-1c; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    STANFORD BACCALAUREATE 1993 Applause for Condoleezza Rice; Don Kennedy; Casper; Cutaways; Schmoozing
  - Stanford Commencement-Tape #1, 06/13/1993; 93-0613-2a; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    Undergraduates, Graduates, Casper, Dianne Feinstein 1993 Stanford Commencement. At the Stanford Stadium, with highlights from the plaque ceremony, baccalaureate, and class day. Dianne Feinstein was the speaker
  - Stanford Commencement-Tape #2, 06/13/1993; 93-0613-2b; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    01:10:00
    COMMENCEMENT 1993 Stanford Stadium; Graduation ceremonies; Cutaways; Gerhard Casper; Dianne Feinstein; Award degrees; Hail to Stanford
  - Stanford Commencement-Tape #3, 06/13/1993; 93-0613-2c; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    COMMENCEMENT 1993: Stanford Stadium; Recessional; Hugs and kisses; Stanford Band; Stanford Fight Song (All Right Now)
  - Dean Michael Spence of the Graduate School of Business, Interview, 08/00/1993; 93-0800-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    MICHAEL SPENCE 1993: Dean of the Graduate School of Business Michael Spence, GSB; books start at 27:00; [Former label can be partially seen under the new label. It reads: 930800, GSB6, Tape 2.]
  - CBS File Footage, 08/01/1993; 93-0801-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    CBS FILE FOOTAGE 1993 Japan stock market; Boeing 777 takeoff; Airplanes
  - Everything Baby, Feed, Promo, undated; ZZ0259; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    Announcement, 5 pt. series, promo
  - Condoleezza Rice B-Roll & Stanford Campus Views, undated; ZZ0267; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
  - Levee Animation, undated; ZZ0269; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    [Content of tape is unknown, but may be a copy of 06-0510-2 which contains Simulated SF Bay Delta Levee Breach Animation at trt :35.] Credit: California Department of Water Resources & Resource Management Associates
  - SLAC, B-Roll, Dub, Master, undated; ZZ0271; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
  - Stanford, B-Roll, (A), Original, undated; ZZ0274; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
  - Stanford Promo, undated; ZZ0275; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    Audio: Mixed 1 & 2
  - SIQSS, Stanford Study takes First Look at How Internet is Changing Daily Life, VNR, undated; ZZ0277; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    TRT: 03:40 & B-Roll: 4:00 A study by the Stanford Institute for the Quantitative Study of Society (SIQSS) in 2000 found that increased Internet use correlated with isolating behaviors such as spending less time with friends and family. The more time people spent on the Internet, the less time they spent interacting with humans in the "real world.
  - Stanford Campus Views, undated; ZZ0290; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
  - Dr. Michael Krusch, undated; ZZ0299; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 32)
    00:16:10